Guide to the Spyros P. Skouras Papers M0509
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Spyros P. Skouras Papers
1942-1971
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Skouras, Spyros Panagiotes
M0509
40 Linear Feet
Files concerning Twentieth Century Fox corporate business and film production, correspondence files including many American politicians such as presidents Eisenhower and Nixon, and subject files on Greek Orthodox activities, philanthropy, etc.
Collection Scope and Content Summary
Files concerning Twentieth Century Fox corporate business and film production, correspondence files including many American politicians such as presidents Eisenhower and Nixon, and subject files on Greek Orthodox activities, philanthropy, etc.
Biography
Spyros Skouras was born in Greece and became a naturalized U.S. citizen in 1913. He founded Fox Film Company, which merged with 20th Century in 1935. Skouras was president of 20th Century Fox between 1942 and 1962 and Chairman of the Board between 1962 and 1969. In 1969, his Prudential shipping line acquired Grace Lines and became Prudential-Grace. He was involved in numerous charities, including the Greek War Relief Association.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Spyros S. Skouras, Sr., 1988.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Note that material must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use. Audiovisual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Motion pictures -- United States; United States -- Politics and government -- 1953-1961.; Niarchos, Stavros.; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994; Churchill, Winston; National Association of Manufacturers.; Neal, Patricia; Papadeas, Georg L.; Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson; Nizer, Louis; Onassis, Aristotle Socrates; Lindsay, John Vliet.; Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1850-1924; Kennedy, Robert F.; McCormack, John W.; Nasser, Gamal Abdel; Luce, Clare Boothe; Wagner, Robert F. (Robert Ferd; Van Fleet, James A. (James Alw; Twentieth Century Fox.; Truman, Harry S., 1884-1972; Luce, Henry R. (Henry Robinson); Zanuck, Darryl Francis; Spellman, Francis; Skouras, Spyros Panagiotes; Salvation Army.; Tree, Marietta; Rodgers, Richard; Taylor, Elizabeth; Stratas, Teresa.; Stevenson, Adlai E. (Adlai Ewing); Adams, Sherman; Adler, Buddy; Agnew, Spiro T., 1918-1996; Allen, Irwin; Alperson, Edward L., 1896-1969; American Bible Society; American-Turkish Society; Athåenagoras. I, Ecumenical Pa; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald); Orthodoxos Ekklēsia tēs Hellados; Fisher, Eddie.; Harriman, W. Averell (William Averell); Haile, Selassie. I, Emperor of; Iakovos, Archbishop of the Grr; Hope, Bob; Karamanlis, Konstantinos; Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Bai; Catholic Interracial Council.; Bergman, Ingrid; Church World Service.; Christopher, George.; Cooke, Terence; Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight; Economic Club of New York.
- Series 1: Biographical Material
  - Biographers
    - Berkowitz, Sally (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Would Be (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Biographical Data
    - Biographical Data SPS Approved (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Skouras, Spyros Panagiotes
    - Greek Orthodox Activities (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Human Interest (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Motion Picture Industry Background (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Personal And Family (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 20th Century Fox Activities (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Published Biography
    - "Bailing Out The Fleet" - Time, July 1965 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - "Ex-Greek With Gifts In Hollywood" - Life International, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - "Hands Across The Sea" - Time, June 1944 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - "King Of Fox Studios" (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - "Mighty Musketeers Of The Movies - American Magazine, June 1955 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - "Prudential Shipping Co." - The Compass, June 1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Various Publications (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Biography - Requests
    - Biographical Data (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - SPS Papers (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Bibliographical Material (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - News Clips - General (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Series 2: Personal Subject Files
  - Books
    - Books - General (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Employment Applications
    - Employment Applications -- General (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Greek-Americans
    - Greek-American Historical Data General (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Immigration
    - General (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Toufexis, Constantine (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Tsopei, Corina (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Legislation
    - Legislation - Cultural Exchange Visa (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Medical
    - Medicine & Health - General (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Memberships
    - General (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Mount Kenya Safari Club (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Trips
    - Holy Land (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Middle East, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Russia, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Turkey, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Tributes After Death
    - Final Rights (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Honorary Pallbearers (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Transcript Of Barry Farber Radio Program, Aug-71 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Contributions (Skouras Center)
    - General (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Business Firms (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Friends (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Governmental And Political (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Motion Picture. Industry (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Organizations (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Relatives (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Shipping (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Contributions (Various)
    - Friends (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Motion Picture Industry (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Organizations - Condolences (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Organizations - General (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - In Memoriam Messages - Newspaper (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Flowers - Artists (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Letters & Telegrams
    - Agents & Shippers (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Artists & Performers (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Bankers (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Business Firms (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Business Firms (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Diplomats (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Foreign (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Friends, Vol. I (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Friends, Vol. II (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Friends, Vol. III (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Friends, Vol. IV (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Friends, Vol. V (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Religious (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Shipping (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Governmental And Political (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Labor (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Motion Picture Industry (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Organizations (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Prudential-Grace Employees (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Radio & Press (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Relatives (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Series 3: Correspondence
  - General Correspondence - A To Z
    - A General (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - B General (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Baird, David (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Bourdoures, Peter (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Bruno, Anne Turner (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - C General (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Cornfield, Albert (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - D General (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Delo, David (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Depinet, Ned (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - E General (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - F General (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - G General (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - H General (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Harrison, Alex (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Harrison, Peter (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Heilman, Claude (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - I General (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Ibrahim, Fathi - Personal (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Ibrahim, Fathi - Representations (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Ibrahim, Fathi - Uar Appointments (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - J General (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - James, Tommy (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - K General (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - L General (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Mc General (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - M General (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - N General (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - 0 General (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - P General (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Packard, Arthur (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Papadeas, George (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Q General (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - R General (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - S General (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Skouras Family (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Skouras Family: Fowler, George Jr. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Skouras Family: Fowler Family (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Skouras Family: Relatives In Greece (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Skouras Family: Relatives In Greece (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - T General (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - U General (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - V General (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - W General (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - XYZ General (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence VIPS - A To Z
    - A General (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Adams, Sherman (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Agnew, Spiro (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Annenburg, Walter (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Athenagoras, Patriarch (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - B General (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Bentley, Helen Delich (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Bergman, Ingrid (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - C General (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Caramanlis, Constantine (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Christopher, George (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Churchill, Winston (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Constantine, King Of Greece (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Cooke, Terence Cardinal (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - D General (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - E General (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., General, 1952 - 1956 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., General, 1953-01; Accession 2017-091. (Box 10, Folder 1A)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., General, 1957 - 1959 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., General, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., General, 1961 - 1969 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., Biography (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., "Dinner With Ike" (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., "75th Birthday Dinner" (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., "Salute To Eisenhower" (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - El-Abd, Vhassan (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - F General (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Farley, James (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Fisher, Eddie & Liz (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - G General (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Greek Royal Family (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Gülek, Kasım (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - H General (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Haile Selassie (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Harriman, Averell W. (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Hearst, William (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Heller, Walter (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Hope, Bob (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - I General (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Lakovos, Archbishop (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - J General (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Johnson, President Lyndon (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - K General (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Kennedy Family (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Kennedy, President John F. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Kennedy, Robert (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - L General (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Lakas, President Demetrios (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Leopaldi, King Of Belgium (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Lindsay, Mayor John V. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Luce, Claire Booth (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Luce, Henry R. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Mccormack, John W. (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - M General (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Mountbatten, Lord (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - N General (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Nasser, President, Gamal Abdel (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Neal, Patricia (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Niarchos, Stavros (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Nixon, President Richard, l952-60 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Nixon, President Richard, 1961 - 1968 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Nixon, President Richard, 1969 - 1971 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Nizer, Louis (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - O General (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Onassis, An (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - P General (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Pappas, John (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Pappas, Tom (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Peter, Prince Of Greece (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Peyton, Father (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Q General (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - R General (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Rabb, Maxwell (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Rank, Lord Arthur (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Ricketon, Frank (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Rockefeller, Governor Nelson (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Rodgers, Richard (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Rogers, William (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - S General (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Spelliuan, Cardinal Francis (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Stevenson, Adlai E. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Stratas, Teresa (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - T General (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Tree, Marietta (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Truman, President Harry (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Turkish Officials (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Turley, Clarence (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Turnbull, Ernest (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - U General (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Uar Government Officials (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - V General (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Van Fleet, General James (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - W General (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Wagner, Mayor Robert (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Warner, Jack (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Wilkie, Phillip (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Y General (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Z General (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Zanuck, Darryl (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Zanuck, Richard (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Zeckendorf, William (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Series 4: Twentieth Century Fox
  - Corporate
    - General (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Board Of Directors: General (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Board Of Directors: Resignation Of Chairman (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Board Of Directors: Rosenman, Judge - Chairman (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Skouras, Spyros P. - Election As Chairman: Domestic Comments, no. 1 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Skouras, Spyros P. - Election As Chairman: Domestic Comments, no. 2 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Skouras, Spyros P. - Election As Chairman: Domestic Comments, no. 3 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Skouras, Spyros P. - Election As Chairman: Foreign Comments, no. 1 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Skouras, Spyros P. - Election As Chairman: Foreign Comments, no. 2 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Executive committee (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Resignation Of President: General Ia (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Resignation Of President: General Ib (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Resignation Of President: General IIa (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Resignation Of President: General IIb (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Interim Presidency (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Stockholders: General, 1948 - 1960 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Stockholders: General, 1961 Jan-Sep (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Stockholders: General, 1961 Oct. - Dec. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Stockholders: General, 1962 - 1968 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Stockholders: Annual Meetings - General (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Stockholders: Annual Meetings, May 16, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Stockholders: Dividends (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Stockholders: Legal (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Stockholders: Skouras Holding And Registration (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Stockholders: Tri-Studio Project (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Stockholders: Zanuck, Darryl F. - Election Of President (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Exhibitors
    - Associations: General (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Associations: Allied States Assn. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Associations: Allied Theatre Owners Of Wisconsin (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Associations: Compo, General (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Associations: Compo, Production Incentive Plan 1 (Motion Picture Fund) (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Associations: Compo,Production. Incentive Plan 2 (Motion Picture Fund) (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Associations: Nato V V (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Associations: Theatre Owners Of America V (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Associations: Theatre Owners Of North And South Carolina (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Associations: United Theatre Owners Of The Heart Of America (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Domestic, General I (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Domestic, General II (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Domestic, Box Office Trends (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Domestic, Circuits, Commonwealth Theatre Company V (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Domestic, Circuits, Georgia Theatre Company (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Domestic, Circuits, Sack, Benjamin (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Domestic, Circuits, Wometco Enterprises (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Domestic, Comments On Studio Executive Meetings I (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Domestic, Comments On Studio Executive Meetings II (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Domestic, Minimum Wage Legislation (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Domestic, Opinion Reports (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Foreign, General (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Foreign, Box Office Trends (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Foreign, India (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Foreign, United Kingdom -Rank Organization (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Tax Reduction (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Theatre (Attendance) Promotion Ideas "Gift-O-Rama" (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Film Festivals, General (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Film Festivals, Moscow Film Festival (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Finance, Foreign Investment Projects (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Finance, Fox, Matthew (Various Fin. Transactions) (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Finance, Pension Plan (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Finance, Salary Reduction Plan (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Home Office Operations - Services (Various) (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Labor - Strike Matters (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Legal, General (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Legal, Divorcement - Antitrust Suit (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Legal, Rosenstein, Jaik Case (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Organizations, Academy Of Motion Picture Arts And Sciences No. 1 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Organizations, Academy Of Motion Picture Arts And Sciences No. 2 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Organizations, American Film Institute (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Organizations, Assn. Of Motion Picture Producers (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Organizations, Motion Picture Assn. Of America, 1957 - 1961 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Organizations, Motion Picture Assn. Of America,1962-64 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Organizations, Motion Picture Assn. Of America,1965-67 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Organizations, Motion Picture Assn. Of America,1968-69 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Organizations, Motion Picture Assn. Of America, TCF Resignation And Rejoining Of (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Organizations, Motion Picture Assn. Of America, Johnson, Eric - Terminal Illness And Suggested Successors Of Pres. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Motion Picture Export Assn. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Motion Picture Pioneers (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Personnel
    - Application For Employment (Studio) (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Branches - General (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Home Office: Administrative And Executive (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Home Office: General (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Home Office: Sales Department (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Special: Hatzipetrov, Hellas 1 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Special: Hatzipetrov,. Hellas 2 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Studio: General (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Studio: Administrative And Executive (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Studio: Talent And Creative (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Production - Films
    - The Agony And The Ecstasy (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Anastasia (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Austerlitz (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - A Certain Smile (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - The Barefoot Battalion (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Battle At Bloody Beach (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - The Big Gamble (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - The Big Show (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Blood And Sand (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - The Blue Angel (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - The Bottom Of The Bottle (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Boy On A Dolphin (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - The Cabinet Of Dr. Caligari (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - The Canadians (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Can-Can (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Carousel (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - The Barbarian And The Geisha (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - The Chapman Report (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - The Comancheros (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Compulsion (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Crack In The Mirror (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Cleopatra - General (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Cleopatra - Actresses Considered (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Cleopatra - Premieres And Requests For Benefit Premieres (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Cleopatra - Advance Ticket Sales & Bookings (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Cleopatra - Prints & Re-Recording (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Cleopatra - Production Progress Reports (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Cleopatra - Publicity & Exploitation: General (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Cleopatra - Publicity & Exploitation: Article In Arab Review Magazine (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Cleopatra - Publicity & Exploitation: Skouras Newsweek Interview, 3/11/63 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Cleopatra - Publicity & Exploitation: Taylor-Burton Adverse Publicity (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Cleopatra - Requests For Tickets (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Cleopatra - Advertising - General (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Cleopatra - Advertising Tie-Ins: General (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Cleopatra - Advertising Tie-Ins: Greyhound Bus Caravan Idea (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Cleopatra - Advertising Tie-Ins: Eastman-Kodak (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Cleopatra's Barge (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Cleopatra - Casting And Budget (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Cleopatra - Clippings (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Cleopatra - The Cleopatra Papers (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Cleopatra - Distribution: General, (1963) (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Cleopatra - Distribution: For Greece (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Cleopatra - Egypt (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Cleopatra - Financial (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Cleopatra - Galatea Films (Rome) (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Cleopatra - Goldstein, Robert (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Cleopatra - Insurance (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Cleopatra - Laudatory Comments (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Cleopatra - London (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Cleopatra - Mamoulian, Rouben (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Cleopatra - Mankiewicz, Joseph (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Cleopatra - Music, Records, Etc. (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Cleopatra - Other Films On Cleopatra (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Cleopatra - Western Costume Co. Lawsuit (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Cleopatra - Zanuck, Darryl F. (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Cleopatra - Reviews, Various (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Cleopatra - Rome (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Cleopatra - Script Changes (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Cleopatra - Souvenir Program (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Cleopatra - Taylor, Elizabeth (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Cleopatra - TCF Studio Facilities (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Cleopatra - Visitors (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Cleopatra - Wanger, Walter (Correspondence) (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Daddy Long-Legs (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Deep Blue Sea (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - De Lux Tour (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Desiree (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Desire In The Dust (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Diamond Safari (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - The Diary Of Anne Frank (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Dr. Doolittle (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - The Enemy Within (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Esther And The King (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - A Farewell To Arms (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Fate Is The Hunter Series 4: Twentieth Century Fox, Production - Films (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Gigot (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - It Happened In Athens - General (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - The Greatest Story Ever Told (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - A Hatful Of Rain (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Hemingway's Adventures Of A Young Man (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Hound Dog Man (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - House Of Bamboo (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - The Hustler (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - The Idiot (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - The Innocents (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Inn Of The Sixth Happiness (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Island In The Sun, 1956-4/30/57 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Island In The Sun, 5/1/1957 - 3/27/58 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - It Happened In Athens - Budget And Finance (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - It Happened in Athens - Casting And Narration (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - It Happened In Athens - Music And Recording (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - It Happened In Athens - Publicity And Clippings (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Journey To The Center Of The Earth (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Kandara (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - The King And I (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Let's Make Love (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - The Lieutenant Wore Skirts (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - The Lion (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Lisa (Box 26, Folder 11)